

#### Personalia

9

Burg. Luytenstraat 12 6151 GG



Munstergeleen 06-41094963



mike.bidinger@ hotmail.com



LinkedIn



GitHub



22-12-1990



Netherlands

#### Languages

NL	•••••
EN	00000
DE	00000

#### Skills

Python	00000
Qlik Sense	00000
MS VBA	00000
MS Office	00000
HTML	00000
CSS	00000
JavaScript	00000
MongoDB	00000
Mendix	00000
VBScripting	00000
Viscom	00000
EDIABAS	00000
SQL	00000
MS Visual C++	00000
MS Visual Basic	00000
MS Visual C#	00000
SAP	00000
LabView	0000

# Mike Bidinger

A true analytical engineer with both data-management and change-management knowledge and experience. Apart from the fact that I already have quite a bit of knowledge, I keep challenging myself and others to broaden my knowledge. My goal is often to realize the best possible reporting and analysis environment for end users. Overseeing the entire process, from the source systems up to and including the analysis, is self-evident. I bring together the functional requirements, organizational interests and technical possibilities within data-driven solutions. This makes me the link between Business and IT and able to understand the question behind the question, to make the translation between customer and technology. In addition, I'm communicatively strong, proactive and I can work independently as well as together within a team.

## **Work Experience**

#### VDL Nedcar, Born

Feb 2018 – present

BDQS (Launch and Change Control, Supply)

Product-data-management specialist and responsible for the product-data-quality. Managing and developing automation processes for efficiency and quality of product related data (back-end). In addition, also responsible for providing the business with accurate information by transforming data into information to enable data-driven decision making (front-end).

#### VDL Nedcar, Born

Dec 2017 – Feb 2018

Change Controller (Launch and Change Control, Supply)

Responsible for the validation, implementation and processing of product-engineering-changes. In addition, a hardware/software product-implementation specialist.

#### **VDL Nedcar, Born**

Jan 2017 - Dec 2017

SQA Line Complaints E/E (Supplier Quality Assurance)

Production disruption support through product quality issues. When by analysis is determined that the is supplier related, complaint costs to the relevant supplier. In addition, responsible for updating software components as a result of engineering changes to the product(s), as well as providing support to the "Rework and Repair" department with the product defect analysis of software components.

**Prodrive Technologies, Son** (Science Park Eindhoven) A Work Preparator, Test Engineer (SMD Assembly)

Aug 2012 – Jan 2017

Responsible for the quality checks through visual test equipment and programming as well as optimizing the SMD production processes through problem analysis (quality and efficiency improvements). In addition, responsible as a work preparator to ensure a high quality and efficiency standard to the start of production for the SMD production processes of new products.

# **Education**

Bachelor (HBO) Electrical Engineering	2008 – 2012
Hogeschool Zuyd Heerlen, Graduated: Yes	

### Courses

Qlik Sense Developer	2022
Qlik Sense Front End Developer	2020
Mendix Rapid Developer	2019
Viscom Release Training	2016
iscom Basic Training	2012